

NAME

Frontend Developer

Aaron Fabricio Santa Cruz Valdez

PERSONAL PROFILE

I studied systems engineering for 5 years and I have been specializing in web development for 3 years. I create, design, update, maintain websites I have extensive knowledge of client side development (Frontend), I have basic knowledge of (Backend) with different technologies. I live in La Paz, Bolivia. I am in constant training learning new web technologies.

CONTACTS



La Paz - Bolivia



aaronfabricio00@gmail.com



+59170668135



https://www.linkedin.com/in/aar on-fabricio-santa-cruz-valdez/



https://aaroncode.net/

EDUCATION

- University Boliviana de Informática
- Platzi(Programming)

ABILITIES

- Web programming.
- Frontend Developer
- SEO
- Website audit
- Desktop and mobile web design
- Basic computer hardware technician.
- Basic cell phone technician

TECHNOLOGIES

- HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT
- SASS, LESS, STYLUS.
- MONGODB, MYSQL
- BOOTSTRAP, MATERIALIZE, TAILWINDCSS.
- NPM AND DEPENDENCES
- WEBPACK
- GIT. GITHUB
- REACT JS, ANGULAR
- PHP WITH LARAVEL
- WORDPRESS

WORK EXPERIENCE

Datec

MAY 2022 - SEP 2022

 Consultant and collaborator in the update of the proflexUI4 software design for ATMs

Goosistem

SEP 2021 - OCT 2021

 Development of the website https://goosistem.com/ with HTML CSS and JAVASCRIPT

Acceso+

SEP 2021 - OCT 2021

IT Assistant

LANGUAGES

- Spanish (Advanced)
- English(Reading and writing)



NOMBRE

Frontend Developer

Aaron Fabricio Santa Cruz Valdez

PERFIL PERSONAL

Estudie 5 años en la carrera de ingeniería en sistemas y llevo 3 años especializándome en desarrollo web. Creo, diseño, actualizo, mantengo sitios web Tengo un amplio conocimiento del desarrollo del lado del cliente (Frontend), tengo conocimientos básicos del (Backend) con diferentes tecnologías. Vivo en La Paz, Bolivia. Estoy en constante formación aprendiendo nuevas tecnologías web.

CONTACTOS

La Paz - Bolivia

aaronfabricio00@gmail.com

+59170668135

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aar on-fabricio-santa-cruz-valdez/

https://aaroncode.net/

EDUCACIÓN

- Universidad Boliviana de Informática
- Platzi(Programación)

HABILIDADES

- Programación web.
- Desarrollador Frontend
- SEO
- Auditoria a sitios web
- Diseño web desktop y movil
- Técnico básico hardware Computadores.

TECNOLOGÍAS

- HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT
- SASS, LESS, STYLUS.
- MONGODB, MYSQL
- BOOTSTRAP, MATERIALIZE, TAILWINDCSS.
- NPM Y DEPENDENCIAS
- WEBPACK
- GIT. GITHUB
- REACT JS, ANGULAR
- PHP CON LARAVEL
- WORDPRESS

EXPERIENCIA DE TRABAJO

Datec

MAY 2022 - SEP 2022

 Consultor y colaborador en la actualización del diseño de proflexUI4 software para ATMs

Goosistem

SEP 2021 - OCT 2021

 Desarrollo del sitio web https://goosistem.com/ con HTML CSS y JAVASCRIPT

Acceso+

Mar 2021 - Jul 2021

Auxiliar de IT

IDIOMAS

- Español (Avanzado)
- Ingles (Lectura y escritura)